PHAN THI NHAT LE



Nha Be District, Ho Chi Minh City

0335542692

lephan098765@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Career goal:

• Short-term:

I aim to secure a legal internship at Circle K Viet Nam to apply my legal knowledge in practice, improve my skills in legal research, document review, contract drafting, and administrative legal tasks.

• Long-term:

My goal is to become a highly skilled legal professional specializing in corporate and commercial law. Within the next five years, I aspire to enhance my expertise in legal consulting, contract negotiation, and business compliance, contributing to the growth and risk management of the company. Through continuous learning and practical experience, I aim to develop the ability to provide strategic legal solutions that align with business objectives.

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Law | 2021- present

- Major in Commercial Law
- GPA: 6.7/10

Research project | 2023-2024

- Law on Limitation of Liability for Compensation for Damages in Air Transportation
 - Legal Experience from Some Countries and Recommendations for Vietnam.
- **Key learning**: Improved skills in legal research, contract analysis, and regulatory compliance

IELTS certificate 5.0 | 2021-2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tutor | 05/2022-01/2023

- Taught English to Primary Students
- Checked homework and prepared for new lesson for students

Key learning: Improved communication skills and ability to explain complex concepts—valuable for legal analysis and client interactions.

Part-time waiter at Jimmy's New York Pizza | 06/2023 - Current

- · Welcomed and guided customers
- Managed customer interactions, handled billing and payments, and ensured smooth service operations.
- Served food and ensured customer Satisfaction
- · Handled customer complaints and problem-solving

Key learning: Strong ability to handle client inquiries, internal requests, client service, teamwork, and attention to detail- essential skills for a legal environment.